## JAEHYEONG JO

85, Hoegi-ro, Dongdaemun-gu, Seoul, 02455, Rep. of Korea

Email: harryjo97@kaist.ac.kr \lefthame: https://harryjo97.github.io/ \lefthame Github: /harryjo97

#### RESEARCH INTERESTS

My research interest lies in understanding physical systems through the lens of geometrical structures, especially in the context of generative modeling. Previous works focus on the generation of geometrical structures with diffusion models, including graphs and data on Riemannian manifolds, and their applications to real-world tasks, e.g., drug discovery, protein design, and neural architecture search.

#### **PREPRINTS**

#### Identity Decoupling for Multi-Subject Personalization of Text-to-Image Models

Sangwon Jang\*, <u>Jaehyeong Jo</u>\*, Kimin Lee<sup>†</sup>, Sung Ju Hwang<sup>†</sup> Preprint, 2024

\*: equal contribution, †: equal advising

#### CONFERENCE PUBLICATIONS

### Generative Modeling on Manifolds Through Mixture of Riemannian Diffusion Processes

Jaehyeong Jo, Sung Ju Hwang

International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML), 2024

#### Graph Generation with Diffusion Mixture

Jaehyeong Jo\*, Dongki Kim\*, Sung Ju Hwang

International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML), 2024

#### DiffusionNAG: Task-guided Neural Architecture Generation with Diffusion Models

Sohyun An\*, Hayeon Lee\*, <u>Jaehyeong Jo</u>, Seanie Lee, Sung Ju Hwang International Conference on <u>Learning Representations</u> (ICLR), 2024

# Text-Conditioned Sampling Framework for Text-to-Image Generation with Masked Generative Models

Jaewoong Lee\*, Sangwon Jang\*, <u>Jaehyeong Jo</u>, Jaehong Yoon, Yunji Kim, Jin-Hwa Kim, Jung-Woo Ha, Sung Ju Hwang

International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV), 2023

#### Exploring Chemical Space with Score-based Out-of-distribution Generation

Seul Lee, Jaehyeong Jo, Sung Ju Hwang

International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML), 2023

# Score-based Generative Modeling of Graphs via the System of Stochastic Differential Equations

Jaehyeong Jo\*, Seul Lee\*, Sung Ju Hwang

International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML), 2022

#### Edge Representation Learning with Hypergraphs

<u>Jaehyeong Jo</u>\*, Jinheon Baek\*, Seul Lee\*, Dongki Kim, Minki Kang, Sung Ju Hwang Neural Information Processing Systems (**NeurIPS**), 2021

\*: equal contribution, †: equal advising

#### RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

#### MLAI (Machine Learning & Artificial Intelligence) Lab, KAIST

Seoul, Korea

Research Assistant (Advisor: Prof. Sung Ju Hwang)

Sep. 2021 - Present

· Conducting research on diffusion-based generative models with applications to real-world tasks such as drug discovery.

Kimlab, UofT Toronto, Canada

Visiting student (Host: Prof. Philip Kim)

Feb. 2023 - Feb. 2023

· Conducting research on protein generative model with diffusion models.

#### PAI (Probability Artificial Intelligence) Lab, KAIST

Daejeon, Korea

Research Assistant (Advisor: Prof. Ganguk Hwang)

Mar. 2020 - Aug. 2021

· Conducted research on graphs (edge representation learning using hypergraph structure).

#### **TALKS**

### Generation of Graph-Structured Data with Diffusion Models

Toronto, Canada

in University of Toronto (UofT)

Feb 2023

#### Score-based Generative Modeling of Graphs via the SDEs

Online Oct. 2022

in LoGaG: Learning on Graphs and Geometry Reading Group

000. 2022

#### Learning with Graph Structure Data

in Pohang University of Science and Technology (POSTECH)

Pohang, Korea July 2022

#### Score-based Graph Generation for Material Design

in Samsung Advanced Institute of Technology (SAIT)

Suwon, Korea Jun. 2022

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

Seoul, Korea

Ph.D. in Artificial Intelligence

Advisor: Prof. Sung Ju Hwang

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

Daejeon, Korea

Sep. 2021 - Present

M.S. in Mathematical Sciences

Mar. 2020 - Aug. 2021

Mar. 2016 - Feb. 2020

Advisor: Prof. Ganguk Hwang

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

Daejeon, Korea

B.S. in Mathematical Sciences

Minor in Computer Science & Engineering

GPA: 3.75/4.3

#### Conference Reviewers

ACADEMIC SERVICES

- · Learning on Graphs Conference (LoG), 2022, 2023
- · International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR), 2022, 2023
- · Conference on Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS), 2022, 2023
- · International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML), 2022, 2023